edgecast.com 2008-06-23

# Content Delivery Network (CDN) || Streaming Video, Audio and Media ||Edgecast - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

EdgeCast Networks, Inc. (EdgeCast) is committed to protecting the privacy of its clients. EdgeCast will not distribute, sell, or rent names, email addresses, or any other personally identifiable information to any third party. EdgeCast may share non-personal, non-individual information collectively with its marketing partners strictly for its own research purposes. For example, EdgeCast will not provide specifics around who purchased a specific product, but rather how many customers purchased that product. Member profile information (e.g. name, title, address, items purchased) may be used to create personalized content, offers, services, and advertising to be used only by EdgeCast. 

**Third Party Content**  
EdgeCast Web sites may contain content from third-party content providers; however the content provider(s) will not receive EdgeCast user or customer information from EdgeCast. 

**Cookies**  
EdgeCast and/or third parties may use cookies to compile statistical data in order to analyze how visitors use the EdgeCast web site. The process may involve setting cookies on local systems in order to gather the necessary information to perform the statistical analysis. The information collected is designed to measure the performance of various marketing initiatives and overall website performance. This information can include the link and referral web site, as well as activity on the EdgeCast web site, including dates and information submitted on EdgeCast's site. 

**Log Files**  
EdgeCast uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are in no way linked to personally identifiable information for the purposes of EdgeCast's usage. 

**Surveys**  
EdgeCast's site occasionally requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary. Information requested may include contact and demographic information. Survey data may be used to monitor or improve the use and satisfaction of EdgeCast's web site, products, or services. EdgeCast will retain ownership to all data provided via voluntary surveys. 

**Links**  
EdgeCast's web site contains links to other sites. Such other sites are not under the control of EdgeCast. Therefore, EdgeCast makes no representations as to the accuracy or integrity of the content included on such other sites. 

When you access a non-EdgeCast web site, you do so at your own risk and EdgeCast is not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any information, data, opinions, advice, or statements made on these sites. EdgeCast provides these links merely as a convenience, and the inclusion of such links does not imply that EdgeCast endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or uses of such web sites. EdgeCast encourages all of its visitors to read the individual privacy statements of such web sites. The EdgeCast Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by the EdgeCast web site. 

Additionally, while the EdgeCast web site may be accessed from countries around the world and contains references to EdgeCast products, services, and programs, such references do not obligate EdgeCast to provide such products, services, or programs in every country. 

**Opt-Out Policy**  
Please email privacy@edgecast.com if you no longer wish to receive information from EdgeCast. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
EdgeCast reserves the right to modify this EdgeCast Privacy Statement, and may modify the Statement from time to time at the EdgeCast Privacy Statement web page. 

**Additional Information**  
If you have any questions about this EdgeCast Privacy Statement or the practices of this web site, email [privacy@edgecast.com](mailto:privacy@edgecast.com)

|
